You're done!
Nothing you've got compares to
these guys' righteous hearts!
They're gonna make you pay!
Can you feel it, Yoshikage Kira?
The truth is staring
you right in the face!
You're nothing compared to them!
This has to be a bad dream.
There's no other explanation.
Things like this just don't happen to me.
It's impossible!
Such an outrage would
befall me only in a dream.
Nah, it's the real deal,
and you're going down.
I guess this means your
good fortune's run out.
You're through, murderer.
Look, Josuke's been
clobbered to a bloody mess.
Given the state of his injuries, it seems
they've been battling a little while now,
which means we're looking at...
The one and only Yoshikage Kira.
We have a bleeder over here!
Someone bring over an ambulance
and get a stretcher now!
Sir, can you hear me?
If you can hear me, there's
an ambulance on the way.
Rest assured, you're in very good hands.
Don't do it!
Get away from her!
We'll be taking you to
the hospital momentarily.
Just stay with me, alright?
Don't worry, you'll be fine.
No, we were too slow!
Kira's already turned that
medical lady into a bomb!
How many fingers am I holding up?
Jotaro, it's time to use Star Platinum.
I'm well aware, but I'm not close
enough for it to be effective.
At this distance,
stopping time is useless.
He's too far away to damage.
I need to get at least
five meters closer to him.
So he's going to hold her
hostage as a human bomb.
Go ahead and blow her up if you're so bad.
I'll fix her faster than
you can say, Deadly Queen!
Josuke, just keep your cool!
Kira blowing up the hostage
is the least of our worries!
I couldn't tell you before, but
he's been hiding a secret power!
It's called Fights the Dust, and
he can use it to obliterate time!
His ability manifests
itself with non-stand users,
normal people like me and that lady.
That's why I couldn't talk to
you guys in the other timelines!
It only appears when Kira screws
the pooch and runs out of options!
That's the exact situation
we're in right now!
He's spiraling into the
deepest pits of despair.
So he's made a bomb that
turns back time by one hour.
This day just keeps getting worse
It's so beautiful your
elegant hand its silky smooth
knuckles and your Zeppeli
soft skin It's so pure.
I'd even call it milky.
May I use your gorgeous
hand to caress my cheek?
It soothes my soul and brings
relief to my restless spirit
When I was a young boy,
I remember discovering Leonardo
da Vinci's enigmatic Mona
Lisa while leafing through a
tome of the Master's works.
It was my first time laying eyes on her.
The beauty before me, well,
it aroused something in me.
It gave me a rock-hard cock.
I cut off her hands and proudly
displayed the treasures in my room.
Now I lust to sever your treasures.
Sir, please, what do
you think you're doing?
The truth is, my name is Yoshikage Kira.
I've had the pleasure of killing 48 beautiful
women with even more beautiful hands.
But you're a special beauty.
You will be the only one to have
ever known my true identity.
Guys, this isn't good!
Bites the Dust is about to activate!
Quickly, we have to kill him right now!
If we let Kira live, everyone here
besides her will be blown to smithereens!
Jotaro!
What's this, Jotaro?
My hatred for you fools
has manifested bites
the dust and you're charging ahead anyway.
If that's how you want it, you
can stop time for all I care.
In fact, all I want is for
you to back me into a corner.
Once I'm pushed to the brink,
my stand's power will
be triggered and I'll
put you creetins out of
commission permanently.
Jotaro, stop time already!
You can't let him push
Deadly Queen's switch!
What's going on?
I've finally reached
my limit with you all!
Time to die!
Yes, I succeeded!
I activated it!
I made it back safely.
I actually pulled it off.
I was able to activate
Bites of Dust yet again!
I destroyed the antelopers!
At last, my quiet life
of freedom could begin!
Is my mind playing tricks?
Those birds flew right through me.
But that's absurd.
Something isn't right.
Like this street.
I've never once used it to get to work.
Time was reversed by one hour, so I
should be on my way to the office.
What the devil is going on?
Where am I?
And for that matter, when?
Huh?
Oh, that's right.
I put my watch in my breast pocket
after I burned my wrist. Huh?
It can't be!
Why is the watch still
broken? And the time?
It says 8.29.
There's no way I activated Bites the Dust!
This is the watch Hyatel
broke with straight-kept.
It should have returned
to its undamaged state.
Still don't get it, do you?
Well, well.
The Kosaku Kawajiri in Rohan's
photo was really Yoshikage Kira.
So then, the battle's finally over.
Amazing.
The great Yoshikage Kira,
bested by those he'd spit upon.
And who the hell are you, girl?
You forgot about little ol' me?
Typical.
I should have known.
Though it did happen 15 years ago.
Huh?
Something truly horrible must
have happened to you in the end.
Something so harrowing you've lost any
and all recollection of what it was.
Are you another stand user,
you talkative little tart?
No, I'm the bearer of bad news.
You've been sent to this
place because you bit it, bub!
I... what?
Understand now?
This is no standability!
This is proof.
Proof that there's justice
in this world and your
murderous soul will rot
until the end of time.
How about it?
Have I jogged your memory?
Do you remember how you died?
I can't stop time now.
He's too far away.
Don't let him do it, Jotaro!
I finally reached my limit with you all.
Time to die! Die!
Mission success!
The primary target has entered the
five meter active range of act three,
three freeze!
S-H-I-T!
Release me you insignificant pest!
Star Platinum, unleash the world!
Koichi, you're the most
reliable guy I've ever met.
I'll be forever grateful that I was
able to come here and get to know you.
Good grief, though.
That was a close call, but we made it.
Whoa, no!
That's enough. Time in.
Hey, you did it!
Man, that was close!
You haven't beaten me
I'll push that button and
what I do bites the dust
will haunt you all down?
This is far from over
but how he just flew into
the air don't push that
button just wait and see!
I'll blow you to hell if I do I can live
out my days in peace
and quiet his tenacity.
is certainly impressive.
Hey! Stop!
Stop!
You're gonna run over the sky!
Oh, shit!
My god!
The ambulance just ran over that man!
He came out of nowhere. Move!
Pull forward, dammit!
All right, you two.
I need you to get behind the tank.
Get back!
Come on, get back!
I need you to just lie down.
There's nothing we can do.
It was an instantaneous death.
He's dead?
It's so crazy.
It's like he tried to
dive under the ambulance.
I feel responsible for this.
I know there's no excuse
for what happened,
but I didn't have a
chance to restrain him.
Life can be bizarre.
He was pinned between
the asphalt and tire.
The force tore off his face.
Do we know the identity of the victim?
He was Yoshikage Kira.
He told me his name himself.
Kira.
There's an old house in Kotodai
belonging to the Kira family.
I heard there was only one occupant,
so we might not have family.
An accident.
To think an accident would end this.
It all worked out for the best.
The law would never have been able
to give the punishment he deserved.
There was no better outcome.
I...
I never really got along with my
dad when he was still with us.
But even so, I never thought I'd lose him.
I wanted justice for my dad's death.
I wanted someone to bring
his killer to justice.
Remember now, Yoshikage Kira?
That's how your life was
ripped away from you.
Funny how memory works.
I've had just about enough of your games.
Who or what are you?
I'm evidence.
Fifteen years ago,
you didn't have a stand that could
make all of your victims disappear.
That's why, when I was murdered,
it was front page news.
Tell me, does this gash on
my back look familiar to you?
Since I was your very first victim,
maybe you forgot to cut off my hands!
I guess I'm just not that
memorable to you, huh?
That's right, it's you.
Of course, you're Reimi Sugimoto.
Tell me right now what you've been
planning here for the past 15 years!
Huh?
Hold on.
What exactly do you get
out of showing off your
disgusting wound and revealing
your true identity to me?
Now wait just a moment.
Is this the place where one shouldn't
look over their shoulder or else?
My old man once said,
hidden somewhere in this town is a
passage for the souls of the dead.
He told me to never look back
if I ever found myself there.
To do so would invite an unspeakable power
that would drag you
into an abyss of misery.
Now it's just a hunch,
but I get the feeling you only
showed me your back in order to lure
me in front of you so I'd play into
your ghostly hands and turn around.
You were trying to trick me,
weren't you, my spectral strumpet?
Why don't you look for me, hmm?
I would love to see what happens.
Now, let's have us a look.
Turn that pretty little head.
Oh, please.
Did you think I wouldn't prepare
for you pulling a stunt like this?
You're so predictable.
We've been waiting for 15 years.
That was way more than
enough time to prepare.
We?
Yeah, good boy, Arnold!
What?
Yoshikage Kira, your hour
of reckoning has arrived.
Disgusting!
What are these putrid things?
Deadly Queen!
Make whatever this is explode!
Oh, God no!
Where are they going to take me?
Say something, please!
I have to know where they're taking me!
What are they going to do? Reimi!
Dunno.
Although, I doubt we'll be
living in peace and tranquility.
Now, at long last, we can
finally pass on, together.
What?
Are you really leaving us, Reimi?
Surely it wouldn't hurt anything if
you stayed a little while longer.
I mean, you've been like a
guardian angel to this town.
I can't imagine life here without you.
Please, you have to stay. Koichi,
you're very sweet,
but Arnold and I have done everything
we set out to accomplish here.
The time's come for us to leave Mariah.
That's how it has to be.
So, little Rohan,
do you think you're going to cry after
we've gone off to the great beyond?
In your dreams?
What reason would I have to miss you?
You died 15 years ago,
making you a distant memory.
I've said this before, but
spirits should really just let go.
Haunting the world of the
living is so out of style.
A soul's final resting
place isn't here with us,
but exploring the uncharted afterlife.
Fine, I'll say it, alright, but I'm only
doing so because I'll never see you again.
I'll miss you.
Of course I don't want you to go.
Yo.
Hey, you're all here.
So it's all over, Reimi?
Oh, wow.
Looks like everyone showed up.
We've all come to say goodbye.
You guys.
It feels weird to say this
to the dearly departed.
But take care of yourself.
See you on the other side, Kay.
You're an extraordinary young woman, dear.
Oh, Reimi, thank you so
much for all you've done.
You saved this little town when
it needed a savior the most.
Thank you for saying that, Koichi.
But we saved Mariah, all of us together.
As long as we draw breath, no one here
today will ever forget you or your bravery.
Thank you all.
That means the world.
So long, my friends.
Be well.
So long, Reimi. Godspeed.
Rest easy.
Where is he?
It's so late.
I guess he's working overtime.
It would have been nice
if he called, though.
Oh, Hayato, you haven't touched your food.
Hurry up before it gets cold.
If you're waiting for me,
I'll eat when Dad gets home.
Uh, Hayato?
It's okay, Mom.
I'll wait with you.
When dad gets home,
we'll all sit down and eat together,
because that's what a family does, right?
Sure.
Say, am I imagining things, or
have you gotten taller lately?
When all was said and done, our little
Morioh wasn't the town it used to be.
A monster named Yoshikage
Kira swept in like
a plague and had his way
with our beloved home.
Hayato's mother will no doubt wait
for her husband until the end of time.
And Shigechi's parents will never stop
waiting for their special
little man to return.
Whether a son, daughter,
brother, or sister.
Kira's victims belong to parents
who will never give up hope.
And yet, that hope will only
cause their pain to grow deeper?
The question is, what can
we do to lessen this burden?
Will a vile past consume our future,
or will we be able to forge
ahead unfettered by fear?
I wish I could say.
How about it, Jotaro?
You worried about what might
happen when we leave this place?
I am, just a bit.
Because of all of this,
we've had the chance to see how
capable Josuke and his friends are.
And there's one thing I can
say with absolute certainty.
The young people living in this
town are heroes one and all,
and each one of them
possesses a heart of gold.
They've the same righteous hearts we
witnessed on our journey to Egypt.
They carry a spirit of radiance that will
fight for true justice above all else.
I see it in Josuke, as well as the others.
Morio's in good hands with them.
As long as they're here, we
have nothing to worry about.
Hey, old man!
Don't just stand there gawking!
Answer me! Well,
then guess it's time for
me to say goodbye to a
great son who's made his
father so very proud Hey,
remember that picture of mom.
I gave you a while ago.
You don't still have it.
Do you?
Course I do I put it in my
wallet for safe keeping just
like you told me to ah since
I can't tell her in person.
I'll tell you I wish her all
the happiness in the world.
So funny thing about that picture.
I gave you I decided to hang on to a piece
Shining Diamond
Oh wow, you shouldn't have.
Though I'll take it if you insist.
We'll just call this gift
16 years of back allowance.
Besides, think about what
your better half would say.
If you took that picture over you?
Who does that cocky punk think he is?
I'm starting to see that
golden spirit, old man.
And he's seeing it all
the way to the bank!
You take good care of yourself. Help!
The invisible baby's
mother was never found.
So, Joseph Joestar rose to the occasion
and began an adventure as a new dad.
Jotaro Kujo finally
finished a doctoral thesis.
He began on a species
of starfish he found.
on a beach in Mariah, earning him his PhD.
Damn that Josuke!
He's always coming in here and eating
all my food like he owns the place!
Agh!
I'll just drink his juice.
Koichi!
Huh?
Sorry I'm late.
I was making Bind boxes for
us and lost track of the time.
Wow, you actually made us a special lunch?
That's so thoughtful.
Lunchtime can't come soon enough.
Tasty!
Now we're cookin', let the healing begin!
Don't fight it, let the food carry you!
If this works, you'll be a normal
old dad again, isn't that great?
Well, that didn't work.
My skin is so smooth!
Check out my refreshed eyes, the
food hair is out of this world!
Isn't it though?
Thanks to this food, I'm even
more stunningly gorgeous now.
What am I gonna do with myself?
You're simply radiant, you!
Yeah, you're practically beaming.
Mmm, you think so?
Would you say I'm a dazzling
dish of devilish delights?
Well, amigo mio, until next we meet.
I just saw Ko holding hands with a girl,
and she was drop-dead gorgeous. Oh, my!
Are you sure he never mentioned
anything to me about a girlfriend?
Did you hear? Mr. Kira
went missing. Yeah, I did.
They're saying they found him
dead without a face. How freaky.
And just how are you going
to make this up to me?
Say what?
That stupid can you kicked Spray
Juice all over my brand new manga.
So I want to know what you're
going to do to make this right.
Jeez, kid, cry me a river.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
All right, let's get started.
You sure spend a lot of time
staring out into the distance.
You see anything cool?
I just see plain old Morioh.
Exactly, isn't it grand?
I find this town interesting,
quite interesting indeed.
And so, for most, the summer of
1999 slipped away like any other.
Peace had come to Morioh, making
for some pretty great days.
Hey, did you hear?
Hmm?
Apparently, Rohan got caught
shoplifting from Kamehuu.
What a dim shit.
Huh?
Man, that's freaking crazy, if it's true.
What do you mean by it?
I mean it has to be.
Wait, you don't know for sure?
Dumbass.
Well, come on, let's bounce.